liftweightsfaster.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Lift Weights Faster

Official Contest Rules

NO PURCHASE IS NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE WILL NOT INCREASE YOUR CHANCES OF WINNING. ALL FEDERAL, STATE, LOCAL AND MUNICIPAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS APPLY. VOID IN RHODE ISLAND AND WHERE PROHIBITED BY LAW.

1\. Eligibility

Unapologetically Powerful Win a Home gym Contest (the “Contest”) is open to legal residents of the continental (48) United States (excepting Rhode Island) and the District of Columbia who are at least eighteen (18) years old at the time of entry. Employees of Sponsor (as defined below) and other companies associated with the promotion of the Contest, and their respective parents, subsidiaries, affiliates and advertising and promotion agencies, as well as the immediate family (spouse, parents, siblings, and children) and household members of each such employee, are not eligible.

2\. Sponsor

The Contest is sponsored by Sinkler Publishing LLC, a Minnesota Limited Liability Company d/b/a Unapologetically Powerful (“Sponsor”), located at 2100-B Lyndale Ave S, Minneapolis, MN 55405.

3\. Agreement to Official Rules

Entry in the Contest constitutes entrant’s full and unconditional agreement to and acceptance of those Official Rules and the decisions of the Sponsor, which are final and binding. Winning a prize is contingent upon being compliant with these Official Rules and fulfilling all other requirements set forth herein and/or required by applicable law.

4\. Contest Period

The Contest begins on 2015-12-01 00:00:00 and ends on 2015-12-07 10:00:00 (the “Contest Period”). Entries that are submitted before or after the Contest Period will be disqualified. Submissions will be accepted for the duration of the Contest Period.

5\. How to Enter

You may enter the Contest in either of the following ways:

Online: You may enter by visiting our website at the following hyperlink: http://www.unapologeticallypowerful.com/, and following the directions provided to fill out and submit the required entry information. By entering the Contest online, you understand that you will be automatically subscribed to our mailing list, and may receive communications from us from time to time in the future, and you expressly consent to agree to such subscription and communications.

Alternate Method of Entry – By Mail: You may also enter by filling out a standard postcard, postage prepaid, setting forth [the words “Compelling headline goes that summarizes the prize! Entry”, your first and last name, address, city, state, zip code, e-mail address, year and date of birth], and mailing it to [2100-B Lyndale Ave S, Minneapolis, MN 55405, Attn: Jen Sinkler]. If you enter through this alternative method of entry, you will not be subscribed to our mailing list.

Limite one (1) submitted entry per person for the duration of the Contest Period, regardless of method of submission. Entries received in excess of the stated limitation will be void. However, for each friend you persuade to enter the Contest, and to designate you as a referrer, you will receive 10 additional “entries” or chance(s) to win. All entries become the property of the Sponsor and will not be acknowledged or returned.

6.Prize Drawing; Odds of WInning

On or about 2015-12-07 19:00:00, the Sponsor will select the potential winners in a random drawing, without replacement, from among all eligible entries received. The odds of being selected depend on the total number of eligible entries.

7.Winner Notification

The potential winners will be notified by email. The Sponsor will attempt to notify each potential winner via email on or about 2014-03-17 19:00:00. If any potential winner cannot be contacted within five (5) business days after the date of the first attempt to contact him/her, or is disqualified for any reason, the Sponsor may select an alternate potential winner in his/her place at random from the remaining non-winning, eligible entries. Each winner will be required to complete, electronically sign and submit a Declaration of Compliance, in form as provided by Sponsor, within five (5) business days of the date notice or attempted notice is first sent, in order to claim his/her prize. If a potential winner cannot be contacted, or fails toe submit the Declaration of Compliance within the required time period, that potential winner forfeits the prize. If the potential winner is at least 18 but still considered a minor in his/her jurisdiction of residence, Sponsor reserves the right to award the prize in the name of his/her parent or legal guardian, who will be required to sign the Declaration of Compliance on the potential winner’s behalf and fulfill any other requirements imposed on the winner as set forth herein. Potential winners must continue to comply with all terms and conditions of these Official Rules and with applicable law, and winning is contingent upon fulfilling all such requirements. Sponsor will take reasonable steps to ensure that all prizes are fulfilled within approximately thirty (30) calendar days after the conclusion of the Contest (the “Award Period”).

8.Prizes

3 will be awarded. First prize is Home Gym Package, Second prize is a style package, Third prize is a Ultimate Sandbag. Sponsor estimates that the value of the prizes are (in United States Dollars) $1000, $250, $100 respectively.

9.General Conditions

In the event that the operation, security, or administration of the Contest is impaired in any way for any reason, including, but not limited to fraud, virus, bug, worm, unauthorized human intervention or other technical problem, or in the even the Contest is unable to run as planned for any other reason, as determined by Sponsor in its sole discretion, the Sponsor may, in its sole discretion, either (a) suspend the Contest to address the impairment and then resume the Contest in a manner that best conforms to the spirit of these Official Rules or (b) terminate the Contest and, in the event of termination, award the prize at random from among the eligible, non-suspect entries received up to the time of the impairment. The Sponsor reserves the right in its sole discretion to disqualify any individual it finds to be tampering with the entry process or the operation of the Contest or to be acting in violation of these Official Rules or in an unsportsmanlike or disruptive manner. This reserved right is in addition to, and not in lieu of, any other rights and remedies available to Sponsor either in equity or at law. Any attempt by any person to damage the website or undermine the legitimate operation of the Contest may be a violation of criminal and civil law, and should such an attempt be made, the Sponsor reserves the right to seek damages (including attorney fees) and any other remedies from such person to the fullest extent permitted by law. Failure by the Sponsor to enforce any provision of these Official Rules shall not constitute a waiver of that provision.

10.RELEASE AND LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY

BY ENTERING THE CONTEST, ENTRANTS AGREE TO RELEASE AND HOLD HARMLESS THE SPONSOR, OTHER COMPANIES ASSOCIATED WITH THE CONTEST, EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE PARENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES AND ADVERTISING AND PROMOTION AGENCIES, AND EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SHAREHOLDERS, REPRESENTATIVES, AND AGENTS (THE “RELEASED PARTIES”) FROM AND AGAINST ANY CLAIM OR CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH ENTRY OR PARTICIPATION IN THE CONTEST OR RECEIPT OR USE OF THE PRIZE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO: (A) ANY TECHNICAL ERRORS ASSOCIATED WITH THE CONTEST, INCLUDING LOST, INTERRUPTED OR UNAVAILABLE INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER (ISP), NETWORK, SERVER, WIRELESS SERVICE PROVIDER, OR OTHER CONNECTIONS, AVAILABILITY OR ACCESSIBILITY OR MISCOMMUNICATIONS OR FAILED COMPUTER, SATELLITE, TELEPHONE, CELLULAR TOWER OR CABLE TRANSMISSIONS, LINES, OR TECHNICAL FAILURE OR JUMBLED, SCRAMBLED, DELAYED, OR MISDIRECTED TRANSMISSIONS OR COMPUTER HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE MALFUNCTIONS, FAILURES OR DIFFICULTIES; (B) UNAUTHORIZED HUMAN INTERVENTION IN THE CONTEST; (C) MECHANICAL, NETWORK, ELECTRONIC, COMPUTER, HUMAN, PRINTING OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS; (D)APPLICATION DOWNLOADS, (E) ANY OTHER ERRORS OR PROBLEMS IN CONNECTION WITH THE CONTEST, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ERRORS THAT MAY OCCUR IN THE ADMINISTRATION OF THE CONTEST, THE ANNOUNCEMENT OF THE WINNER, THE CANCELLATION OR POSTPONEMENT OF THE EVENT AND/OR THE FLYOVER, IF APPLICABLE, THE INCORRECT DOWNLOADING OF THE APPLICATION THE PROCESSING OF ENTRIES APPLICATION DOWNLOADS OR IN ANY CONTEST-RELATED MATERIALS; OR (F) INJURY, DEATH, LOSSES OR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, TO PERSONS OR PROPERTY WHICH MAY BE CAUSED, DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY, IN WHOLE OR IN PART, FROM ENTRANTS PARTICIPATION IN THE CONTEST OR ACCEPTANCE, RECEIPT OR MISUSE OF THE PRIZE. ENTRANT FURTHER AGREES THAT IN ANY CAUSE OF ACTION, THE RELEASED PARTIES’ AGGREGATE LIABILITY WILL BE LIMITED TO THE COST OF ENTERING AND PARTICIPATING IN THE CONTEST, IF ANY, AND IN NO EVENT SHALL THE ENTRANT BE ENTITLED TO RECEIVE ATTORNEYS FEES OR COSTS OF COURT. RELEASED PARTIES ARE ALSO NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY INCORRECT OR INACCURATE INFORMATION, WHETHER CAUSED BY SITE USERS, TAMPERING, HACKING, OR BY ANY EQUIPMENT OR PROGRAMMING ASSOCIATED WITH OR UTILIZED IN THE CONTEST. SPONSOR HEREBY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS, AND ENTRANT HEREBY EXPRESSLY WAIVES, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY APPLICABLE LAW, THE RIGHT TO CLAIM ANY PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL OR OTHER INDIRECT DAMAGES, HOWSOEVER CAUSED, AND REGARDLESS OF THE LEGAL THEORY ON WHICH SUCH CLAIM MAY BE BASED.

11\. Disputes

Except where prohibited, each entrant agrees that any and all disputes, claims and causes of action arising out of, or connected with, the Contest or any prize awarded shall be resolved individually, without resort to any form of class action, and exclusively by the appropriate court located in Minnesota, and submits to the personal jurisdiction of such courts, waiving any and all objection thereto, including without limitation objection based on forum non conveniens. All issues and questions concerning the construction, validity, interpretation and enforceability of these Official Rules, entrants rights and obligations, or the rights and obligations of the Sponsor in connection with the Contest, shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the laws of Minnesota, without giving effect to any choice of law or conflict of law rules which would cause the application of the laws of any jurisdiction other than Minnesota.

12.Privacy

Information collected from entrants is subject to Sponsor’s privacy policy.

13.Winner List

To request the name(s) of the Contest winner(s), send either: (a) a self-addressed, stamped envelope to [2100-B Lyndale Ave S, Minneapolis, MN 55405, Attn: Jen Sinkler] or (b) an email to jen@jensinkler.com. Winner list requests will only be accepted after the conclusion of the Award Period.  
NO PURCHASE IS NECESSARY.

This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn or Google. You understand that you are providing your information to the owner of this contest and not to Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn or Google.

unapologeticallypowerful.com PRIVACY POLICY

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING ANY PART OF THE WEBSITE.

I. OVERVIEW

Sinkler Publishing LLC (“Jen Sinkler”) recognizes and respects the privacy of users of unapologeticallypowerful.com (the “Website”). The following privacy policy, as modified from time to time by us as described below (the “Policy”), tells you about the information that unapologeticallypowerful.com collects through the Website and how we use the information we may collect. If you access the Website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us.

II. UPDATES

unapologeticallypowerful.com reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time, and will post any revised Policy on this page. You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new updated date at the top of this Policy. unapologeticallypowerful.com will not notify its Website users of any such changes by e-mail or other personal contact. We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit this Website so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications. Please note that this Policy applies to all information collected online by unapologeticallypowerful.com.

III. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you, including but not limited to your name, postal delivery address, e-mail address, payment method (e.g., credit card or debit card) and telephone number, as well as other information when such information is combined with your personal information. When you register or use certain services available on our Website, we ask you to supply us with certain personal information so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts.

For similar reasons, we may supplement the personal information you provide with publicly available information about you. We use this personal information to process your registration, your payments, and to communicate with you on these and other topics. We may also use your e-mail address to send you newsletters, promotional announcements, and consumer surveys. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account transactions.

We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your site activity, payment history and correspondence as well as any other related activity. We use this information for such purposes as personalizing the site to better reflect particular interests, tracking your level of activity, helping us quickly and efficiently respond to inquiries and requests and otherwise enhancing our service offering for our customers. We also provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We may also disclose and otherwise use, on an anonymous basis, site habits, commentary, reviews and other non-personal information about customers.

While using the Website, you will have opportunities to post comments or other personal information in forums, such as the blog. Please understand that when you post such information, it is made public and is not subject to this policy. Please refer to the Website’s Terms of Service, for more information regarding obligations associated with the posting of User Content on the Website.

IV. VIEWING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the truth and accuracy of the personal information you provide to us relating to your account. If you want to update your contact information, you should do so by visiting the Edit Profile section of our Website. You must be signed in to access the Edit Profile.

V. COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY

As you browse the Website, cookies may placed on your computer’s hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive for record keeping purposes.) In general, cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. If your browser is set to not accept cookies, you may not be able to use particular services on the Website.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including pixel tags, to gather information on how our users interact with our Website and to otherwise help us efficiently operate and monitor our site and service. These technologies, show us, for example, popular pages, conversion rates, click-throughs and other information that can be used to improve, operate and monitor our site and our service.

VI. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services on our behalf. For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our Web pages, process credit card transactions, collect debts, analyze and enhance data, including customers’ interaction with our site, and process consumer surveys. In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your personal information. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of providing the services we request of them.

In addition, we often partner with third party companies, agents or contractors in order to offer joint promotions, advertisements, programs and marketing campaigns in which we believe our users may be interested. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of participating in the partnership arrangement for which unapologeticallypowerful.com engages them.

unapologeticallypowerful.com also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law, if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety. In the event that unapologeticallypowerful.com is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right, to sell or otherwise transfer the personal information we have collected as part of that transaction provided that such third party continues to honor our privacy policy.

NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING SET FORTH HEREIN TO THE CONTRARY, unapologeticallypowerful.com RESERVES THE RIGHT TO USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (EXCLUSIVE OF ANY CREDIT CARD INFORMATION PROVIDED, IF ANY) FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE, IN unapologeticallypowerful.com’S SOLE DISCRETION. unapologeticallypowerful.com may use your personal information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, text/short message services, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

VII. SECURITY

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access our Website account. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to the Website.

Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. By using this Website, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this site.

VIII. CONTACT

If you have questions concerning your account, please contact Customer Service. If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please email info@unapologeticallypowerful.com.

Our address is 2100-B Lyndale Ave S., Minneapolis, MN 55405.
